<resources>
    <!-- Djinn Jinxes -->
    <string name="jinx_alchemist_boffin">If the Alchemist has the Boffin ability, the Alchemist does not learn what ability the Demon has.</string>
    <string name="jinx_alchemist_marionette">An Alchemist-Marionette has no Marionette ability &amp; the Marionette is in play.</string>
    <string name="jinx_alchemist_mastermind">An Alchemist-Mastermind has no Mastermind ability &amp; the Mastermind is not-in-play.</string>
    <string name="jinx_alchemist_organgrinder">If the Alchemist has the Organ Grinder ability, the Organ Grinder is in play. If both are sober, both are drunk.</string>
    <string name="jinx_alchemist_spy">An Alchemist-Spy has no Spy ability &amp; a Spy is in play. After each execution, a living Alchemist-Spy may publicly guess a living player as the Spy. If correct, the Demon must choose the Spy tonight.</string>
    <string name="jinx_alchemist_summoner">The Alchemist-Summoner does not get bluffs, and chooses which Demon but not which player. If they die before this happens, evil wins. <b>[No Demon]</b></string>
    <string name="jinx_alchemist_wraith">An Alchemist-Wraith has no Wraith ability &amp; a Wraith is in play. After each execution, a living Alchemist-Wraith may publicly guess a living player as the Wraith. If correct, the Demon must choose the Wraith tonight.</string>
    <string name="jinx_alchemist_widow">An Alchemist-Widow has no Widow ability &amp; a Widow is in play. After each execution, a living Alchemist-Widow may publicly guess a living player as the Widow. If correct, the Demon must choose the Widow tonight.</string>
    <string name="jinx_bountyhunter_kazali">If the Kazali turns the Bounty Hunter into a Minion, an evil Townsfolk is not created.</string>
    <string name="jinx_bountyhunter_philosopher">If the Philosopher gains the Bounty Hunter ability, a Townsfolk might turn evil.</string>
    <string name="jinx_cannibal_butler">If the Cannibal gains the Butler ability, the Cannibal learns this.</string>
    <string name="jinx_cannibal_juggler">If the Juggler guesses on their first day and dies by execution, tonight the living Cannibal learns how many guesses the Juggler got correct.</string>
    <string name="jinx_cannibal_princess">If the Cannibal nominated, executed, &amp; killed the Princess today, the Demon doesn’t kill tonight.</string>
    <string name="jinx_cannibal_zealot">If the Cannibal gains the Zealot ability, the Cannibal learns this.</string>
    <string name="jinx_mathematician_chambermaid">The Chambermaid can detect if the Mathematician will wake tonight.</string>
    <string name="jinx_mathematician_drunk">The Mathematician might learn if the Drunk\'s ability yielded false info or failed to work properly.</string>
    <string name="jinx_mathematician_lunatic">The Mathematician might learn if the Lunatic attacks a different player than the real Demon attacked.</string>
    <string name="jinx_mathematician_marionette">The Mathematician might learn if the Marionette\'s ability yielded false info or failed to work properly.</string>
    <string name="jinx_magician_legion">The Magician wakes with Legion and might register as evil. Legion knows if a Magician is in play, but not which player it is.</string>
    <string name="jinx_magician_marionette">If the Magician is alive, the Demon doesn\'t know which neighbor is the Marionette.</string>
    <string name="jinx_magician_spy">When the Spy sees the Grimoire, the Demon and Magician\'s character tokens are removed.</string>
    <string name="jinx_magician_vizier">If the Vizier is in play, the Magician has no ability but is immune to the Vizier\'s ability.</string>
    <string name="jinx_magician_widow">When the Widow sees the Grimoire, the Demon and Magician\'s character tokens are removed.</string>
    <string name="jinx_magician_wraith">After each execution, the living Magician may publicly guess a living player as the Wraith. If correct, the Demon must choose the Wraith tonight.</string>
    <string name="jinx_butler_organgrinder">If the Organ Grinder is causing eyes closed voting, the Butler may raise their hand to vote but their vote is only counted if their master voted too.</string>
    <string name="jinx_heretic_baron">Only 1 jinxed character can be in play.</string>
    <string name="jinx_heretic_godfather">Only 1 jinxed character can be in play.</string>
    <string name="jinx_heretic_lleech">Only 1 jinxed character can be in play.</string>
    <string name="jinx_heretic_pithag">Only 1 jinxed character can be in play.</string>
    <string name="jinx_heretic_spy">Only 1 jinxed character can be in play.</string>
    <string name="jinx_heretic_widow">Only 1 jinxed character can be in play.</string>
    <string name="jinx_plaguedoctor_baron">If the Storyteller would gain the Baron ability, up to two players become Outsiders.</string>
    <string name="jinx_plaguedoctor_boomdandy">If the Storyteller would gain the Boomdandy ability, a player becomes the Boomdandy.</string>
    <string name="jinx_plaguedoctor_evil_twin">If the Storyteller would gain the Evil Twin ability, a player becomes the Evil Twin.</string>
    <string name="jinx_plaguedoctor_fearmonger">If the Storyteller would gain the Fearmonger ability, a Minion gains it, and learns this.</string>
    <string name="jinx_plaguedoctor_goblin">If the Storyteller would gain the Goblin ability, a Minion gains it, and learns this.</string>
    <string name="jinx_plaguedoctor_marionette">If the Storyteller would gain the Marionette ability, one of the Demon\'s good neighbors becomes the Marionette.</string>
    <string name="jinx_plaguedoctor_scarletwoman">If the Storyteller would gain the Scarlet Woman ability, a Minion gains it, and learns this.</string>
    <string name="jinx_plaguedoctor_spy">If the Storyteller would gain the Spy ability, a Minion gains it, and learns this.</string>
    <string name="jinx_plaguedoctor_wraith">If the Storyteller would gain the Wraith ability, a Minion gains it, and learns this.</string>
    <string name="jinx_recluse_ogre">If the Recluse registers as evil to the Ogre, the Ogre learns that they are evil.</string>
    <string name="jinx_recluse_sage">The Recluse might register as the Demon to the Sage.</string>
    <string name="jinx_boffin_cultleader">If the Demon has the Cult Leader ability, they can’t turn good due to this ability.</string>
    <string name="jinx_boffin_drunk">The Demon cannot have the Drunk ability.</string>
    <string name="jinx_boffin_goon">If the Demon has the Goon ability, they can’t turn good due to this ability.</string>
    <string name="jinx_boffin_heretic">The Demon cannot have the Heretic ability.</string>
    <string name="jinx_boffin_ogre">The Demon cannot have the Ogre ability.</string>
    <string name="jinx_boffin_politician">The Demon cannot have the Politician ability.</string>
    <string name="jinx_boffin_villageidiot">If there is a spare token, the Boffin can give the Demon the Village Idiot ability.</string>
    <string name="jinx_cerenovus_goblin">The Cerenovus may choose to make a player mad that they are the Goblin.</string>
    <string name="jinx_marionette_balloonist">If the Marionette thinks that they are the Balloonist, an Outsider might have been added during setup.</string>
    <string name="jinx_marionette_huntsman">If the Marionette thinks that they are the Huntsman, the Damsel was added during setup.</string>
    <string name="jinx_marionette_kazali">If there would be a Marionette in play, they enter play after the Demon &amp; must start as their neighbor.</string>
    <string name="jinx_marionette_lilmonsta">If there would be a Marionette in play, they enter play after the Demon &amp; must start as their neighbor.</string>
    <string name="jinx_marionette_summoner">If there would be a Marionette in play, they enter play after the Demon &amp; must start as their neighbor.</string>
    <string name="jinx_mastermind_vigormortis">A Mastermind that has their ability keeps it if the Vigormortis dies.</string>
    <string name="jinx_pithag_cultleader">If the Pit-Hag turns an evil player into the Cult Leader, they can\'t turn good due to their own ability.</string>
    <string name="jinx_pithag_damsel">If a Pit-Hag creates a Damsel, the Storyteller chooses which player it is.</string>
    <string name="jinx_pithag_goon">If the Pit-Hag turns an evil player into the Goon, they can\'t turn good due to their own ability.</string>
    <string name="jinx_pithag_ogre">If the Pit-Hag turns an evil player into the Ogre, they can\'t turn good due to their own ability.</string>
    <string name="jinx_pithag_politician">If the Pit-Hag turns an evil player into the Politician, they can\'t turn good due to their own ability.</string>
    <string name="jinx_pithag_villageidiot">If there is a spare token, the Pit-Hag can create an extra Village Idiot. If so, the drunk Village Idiot might change.</string>
    <string name="jinx_scarletwoman_alhadikhia">If there would be two Demons, one of which was the Scarlet Woman, the Scarlet Woman becomes the Scarlet Woman again.</string>
    <string name="jinx_scarletwoman_fanggu">If there would be two Demons, one of which was the Scarlet Woman, the Scarlet Woman remains the Scarlet Woman.</string>
    <string name="jinx_spy_damsel">If the Spy is (or has been) in play, the Damsel is poisoned.</string>
    <string name="jinx_spy_ogre">The Spy registers as evil to the Ogre.</string>
    <string name="jinx_spy_poppygrower">If the Poppy Grower has their ability, the Spy does not see the Grimoire.</string>
    <string name="jinx_summoner_clockmaker">The Summoner registers as the Demon to the Clockmaker.</string>
    <string name="jinx_summoner_courtier">If the living Summoner has no ability, the Storyteller has the Summoner ability.</string>
    <string name="jinx_summoner_engineer">If the living Summoner is removed from play, the Storyteller has the Summoner ability.</string>
    <string name="jinx_summoner_hatter">If the Summoner creates a second living Demon, deaths tonight are arbitrary.</string>
    <string name="jinx_summoner_kazali">If the Summoner creates a second living Demon, deaths tonight are arbitrary.</string>
    <string name="jinx_summoner_lordoftyphon">If a Lord of Typhon is summoned, they must neighbor a Minion &amp; their other neighbor becomes an evil Minion.</string>
    <string name="jinx_summoner_pithag">If the Summoner creates a second living Demon, deaths tonight are arbitrary.</string>
    <string name="jinx_summoner_poppygrower">If the Poppy Grower is alive on the 3rd night, the Summoner chooses which Demon but not which player.</string>
    <string name="jinx_summoner_preacher">If the living Summoner has no ability, the Storyteller has the Summoner ability.</string>
    <string name="jinx_summoner_pukka">The Summoner may summon a Pukka on the 2nd night instead of the 3rd.</string>
    <string name="jinx_summoner_zombuul">If the Summoner summons a dead player into the Zombuul, the Zombuul has already \"died once\".</string>
    <string name="jinx_vizier_alsaahir">The Storyteller doesn\'t declare the Vizier is in play.</string>
    <string name="jinx_vizier_courtier">If the Vizier loses their ability, they learn this, and cannot die during the day.</string>
    <string name="jinx_vizier_fearmonger">The Vizier wakes with the Fearmonger, learns who they choose and cannot choose to immediately execute that player.</string>
    <string name="jinx_vizier_investigator">The Storyteller doesn\'t declare the Vizier is in play.</string>
    <string name="jinx_vizier_politician">The Politician might register as evil to the Vizier.</string>
    <string name="jinx_vizier_preacher">If the Vizier loses their ability, they learn this, and cannot die during the day.</string>
    <string name="jinx_vizier_zealot">The Zealot might register as evil to the Vizier.</string>
    <string name="jinx_widow_damsel">If the Widow is (or has been) in play, the Damsel is poisoned.</string>
    <string name="jinx_widow_poppygrower">If the Poppy Grower has their ability, the Widow does not see the Grimoire.</string>
    <string name="jinx_alhadikhia_princess">If the Princess nominated &amp; executed a player on their 1st day, no one dies to the Al-Hadikhia tonight.</string>
    <string name="jinx_alhadikhia_mastermind">If the Al-Hadikhia dies by execution, and the Mastermind is alive, the Al-Hadikhia chooses 3 good players tonight: if all 3 choose to live, evil wins. Otherwise, good wins.</string>
    <string name="jinx_legion_engineer">If Legion is created, all evil players become Legion. If Legion is in play, the Engineer starts knowing this but has no ability.</string>
    <string name="jinx_legion_hatter">If Legion is created, all evil players become Legion. If Legion is in play, the Hatter has no ability.</string>
    <string name="jinx_legion_minstrel">If Legion died by execution today, Legion keeps their ability, but the Minstrel might learn they are Legion.</string>
    <string name="jinx_legion_politician">The Politician might register as evil to Legion.</string>
    <string name="jinx_legion_preacher">If the Preacher chooses Legion, Legion keeps their ability, but the Preacher might learn they are Legion.</string>
    <string name="jinx_legion_summoner">If Legion is summoned, all evil players become Legion.</string>
    <string name="jinx_legion_zealot">The Zealot might register as evil to Legion.</string>
    <string name="jinx_leviathan_banshee">Each night*, the Leviathan chooses an alive good player (different to previous nights): a chosen Banshee dies &amp; gains their ability.</string>
    <string name="jinx_leviathan_exorcist">If the Leviathan nominates and executes the Exorcist-chosen player, good wins.</string>
    <string name="jinx_leviathan_farmer">Each night*, the Leviathan chooses an alive good player (different to previous nights): a chosen Farmer uses their ability but does not die.</string>
    <string name="jinx_leviathan_grandmother">If the Leviathan is in play and the Grandchild dies by execution, evil wins.</string>
    <string name="jinx_leviathan_hatter">The Leviathan cannot enter play after day 5.</string>
    <string name="jinx_leviathan_innkeeper">If the Leviathan nominates and executes an Innkeeper-protected player, good wins.</string>
    <string name="jinx_leviathan_king">If the Leviathan is in play, and at least 1 player is dead, the King learns an alive character each night.</string>
    <string name="jinx_leviathan_mayor">If the Leviathan and the Mayor are alive on day 5 &amp; no execution occurs, good wins.</string>
    <string name="jinx_leviathan_monk">If the Leviathan nominates and executes the Monk-protected player, good wins.</string>
    <string name="jinx_leviathan_pithag">The Leviathan cannot enter play after day 5.</string>
    <string name="jinx_leviathan_ravenkeeper">Each night*, the Leviathan chooses an alive player (different to previous nights): a chosen Ravenkeeper uses their ability but does not die.</string>
    <string name="jinx_leviathan_sage">Each night*, the Leviathan chooses an alive good player (different to previous nights): a chosen Sage uses their ability but does not die.</string>
    <string name="jinx_leviathan_soldier">If the Leviathan nominates and executes the Soldier, good wins.</string>
    <string name="jinx_lilmonsta_hatter">If the Hatter dies &amp; the Demon chooses Lil\' Monsta, they also choose a Minion to become.</string>
    <string name="jinx_lilmonsta_poppygrower">If Lil\' Monsta &amp; the Poppy Grower are alive, Minions wake one by one, until one of them chooses to take the Lil\' Monsta token.</string>
    <string name="jinx_lilmonsta_psychopath">If the Psychopath is babysitting Lil\' Monsta, they die when executed.</string>
    <string name="jinx_lilmonsta_magician">If the Magician is alive, the Storyteller chooses which Minion babysits Lil\' Monsta.</string>
    <string name="jinx_lilmonsta_scarletwoman">If Lil\' Monsta dies with 5 or more players alive, the Scarlet Woman babysits Lil\' Monsta for the rest of the game.</string>
    <string name="jinx_lilmonsta_vizier">If the Vizier is babysitting Lil\' Monsta, they die when executed.</string>
    <string name="jinx_lleech_mastermind">If the Mastermind is alive and the Lleech host dies by execution, the Lleech lives but loses their ability.</string>
    <string name="jinx_lleech_slayer">If the Slayer slays the Lleech host, the host dies.</string>
    <string name="jinx_riot_atheist">During a riot, if the Storyteller is nominated, players vote. If they are \"about to die\", the game ends. If not, they nominate again.</string>
    <string name="jinx_riot_banshee">Each night*, Riot chooses an alive good player (different to previous nights): a chosen Banshee dies &amp; gains their ability.</string>
    <string name="jinx_riot_exorcist">If Riot nominates and executes the Exorcist-chosen player, good wins.</string>
    <string name="jinx_riot_farmer">Each night*, Riot chooses an alive good player (different to previous nights): a chosen Farmer uses their ability but does not die.</string>
    <string name="jinx_riot_grandmother">If Riot is in play and the Grandchild dies by execution, evil wins.</string>
    <string name="jinx_riot_innkeeper">If Riot nominates and executes an Innkeeper-protected player, good wins.</string>
    <string name="jinx_riot_king">If Riot is in play, and at least 1 player is dead, the King learns an alive character each night.</string>
    <string name="jinx_riot_mayor">The Mayor may choose to stop the riot. If they do so when only 1 Riot is alive, good wins. Otherwise, evil wins.</string>
    <string name="jinx_riot_monk">If Riot nominates and executes the Monk-protected player, good wins.</string>
    <string name="jinx_riot_ravenkeeper">Each night*, Riot chooses an alive good player (different to previous nights): a chosen Ravenkeeper uses their ability but does not die.</string>
    <string name="jinx_riot_sage">Each night*, Riot chooses an alive good player (different to previous nights): a chosen Sage uses their ability but does not die.</string>
    <string name="jinx_riot_soldier">If Riot nominates and executes the Soldier, good wins.</string>
    <string name="jinx_vortox_banshee">If the Vortox kills the Banshee, all players learn that the Banshee has died.</string>
    <string name="jinx_yaggababble_exorcist">If the Exorcist chooses the Yaggababble, the Yaggababble does not kill tonight.</string>
</resources>